"生活大爆炸" 前情提要...
Previously on The Big Bang Theory...
看看那胸毛
Oh, look at all that chest hair.
和龅牙
And overbite.
你当然是我Wolowitz家人
Of course you're a Wolowitz.
狗崽子! 他咬我!
Son of a bitch, he bit me.
安全起见 我还是去一趟急诊室吧
Okay, I guess I'll just go to the emergency room to be safe.
Howie 你想太多了
Howie, this is just your hypochondria.
不 当我坐在了静音键上 却以为自己聋了的时候
When I sat on the mute button and thought I'd gone deaf,
那才是我想太多
that was my hypochondria.
我们换个时间再告诉他我怀孕了吧
We'll find another time to tell him I'm pregnant.
现在
早上好
Morning.
"我们"?
"We"?
这是什么?
What is this?
我不知道啊
I don't know.
大概背面也写了什么吧
Maybe it says something on the back.
"继续看牛奶上的线索"
"Continued on milk."
如果你想引诱我去自己做早饭的话
If you're tricking me into making my own breakfast,
我妈早就用过这招了 你用这招也没用
it didn't work for my mom, and it won't work for you.
"是"
"Are."
" 我们是... "
"We are..."
"再看看勺子上"
"See spoons for more."
会是啥呢?
What could it be?
"我们是格鲁特"?
"We are Groot"?
"银河护卫队" 中的树人格鲁特 他只会说"我是格鲁特"
"我们是冠军"?
"We are the champions"?
皇后乐队（Queen）最著名的单曲之一
"我们是一家人"?
"We are family"?
一首非常有名的歌曲，原唱者Sister Sledge
"我拥有一帮好姐妹"
"I got all my sisters with me."
你是认真的吗?
Are you serious?
是的
Yeah.
你确定吗?
Are you sure?
(positive亦有 阳性 之意)
非常确定
Pretty positive.
那是个玩笑 但是我的验孕棒显示...
That's a joke, because the pregnancy test says...
天啊
Oh, my God.
太棒了
This is incredible.
我们要当父母了?
We're gonna be parents?
我们终于可以优先上飞机了
We're gonna get to board planes first.
终于可以去看看
Finally gonna get to see
商场里的家庭厕所了
what's in that family bathroom at the mall.
是啊 太激动人心了
I know, it's crazy.
太激动人心了
It is crazy.
你怎么... 为宝宝的到来做好准备呢?
I mean, how do you... prepare for something like this?
我以前好像都没有抱过宝宝
I'm not even sure I've held a baby before.
没事的 你会摸索出来的
Oh, it's okay, you'll figure it out.
但是我们该怎么做?
But how's this all gonna work?
要请保姆吗?
Do we get a nanny?
我们请得起保姆吗?
I mean, can we afford a nanny?
假如请得起 不能请个漂亮的
And if we can, we can't get a pretty one,
因为她会毁掉我们的婚姻
'cause it'll wreck our marriage.
我们不能请丑的来 因为会把宝宝吓坏了的
We can't get an ugly one, 'cause it'll scare the kid.
我也不知道 Howie
I-I don't know, Howie.
咱们是住在好学区里吗?
Are we in a good school district?
你是天主教 我是犹太教
You're Catholic, I'm Jewish.
孩子应该信哪种教?
What religion do we raise it?
如果是男孩子 要不要给他割包皮?
And if it's a boy, do we get him circumcised?
人们都说这太野蛮了
People say it's barbaric,
但是不去割 看起来又像煎饼卷油条
but if we don't, it looks like a pig in a blanket.
淡定淡定 没事的
Calm down, it's gonna be okay.
怎么会没事?
How's it gonna be okay?
看我呀 我自己都一团糟
Look at me, I'm a mess.
那就说明 宝宝会是半团糟
And that means this baby's gonna half a mess.
而且现在我们还没吓坏那个
And that's even before we screw it up
物美价廉长相平庸的保姆 就已经糟透了
with our cut-rate moderately attractive nanny.
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall * * We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第九季第16集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调:酥酥是学酥
校对: UUUUUU
翻译：猫呗 肉肉君 波特妹子
翻译：舒大卷子 無限月讀 李小宝Licht
嘿 Raj 我听说你们系里面有几个人
Hey, Raj, I read a couple guys in your department
可能在太阳系里发现了一个新的行星?
may have discovered a new planet in our solar system?
嗯 我听说了
Oh, I heard about that.
为什么不是你发现的?
Why didn't you discover it?
因为为了做果酱 假期送你们
Because instead of being in the telescope room,
我没能去成望远镜室
I was busy making you guys homemade jam for the holidays.
如果你得了诺贝尔博伊森莓奖
Well, you be sure to let us know
要记得通知我们
when you win the Nobel Prize for boysenberry.
嘿
Hey.
- 你好  - 嘿 哥们
- Hello.  - Hey, bud.
等你准备好就开始
Ready to play when you are.
嗯 稍微等下
Yeah, um, in a minute.
我得和你们说些事情
I actually need to tell you guys something.
如果你要感谢我给你们
If it's "thank you" for the homemade jam
在十二月做的果酱 恭喜
you got in December, congratulations,
你是第一个
you're the first one.
什么事?
What's going on?
我 嗯...
I'm, uh...
要当爸爸了
uh, gonna be a father.
- 太棒了!  - 恭喜
- That's so amazing. What?  - Congratulations.
不要啊
Oh, no.
为啥"不要啊"?
Why "oh, no"?
因为这会改变一切
Because this changes everything.
漫画之夜怎么办?
What about comic book night?
我们还能一起玩游戏吗?
Uh, what about playing games together?
我们去迪斯尼的计划呢?
What about our trips to Disneyland?
带着孩子我们怎么做这些事啊?
How can we do those things with a child around?
别激动 我们圈子里容得下两个宝宝
Relax, there's room for two babies in this group.
哦 天...
Oh, dear L...
Penny也怀孕了?
Penny's pregnant, too?
另外一个宝宝是你
You're the other baby.
哦 是吗?
Oh, really?
好 一个孩子需要每隔11天就刮胡子吗?
Okay, well, would a baby have to shave once every 11 days?
一个成年人会拒绝吃
Would an adult refuse to eat his graham crackers
碎了一点的全麦饼干吗?
because one of them was broken?
我们扯平了
I guess we'll call this a draw.
跟高兴你们能来这里
So, I'm glad you guys are here.
我想和你们说些事情
There's something I want to share with you.
Howie和我准备...
Howie and I are going to...
Leonard说你怀孕了
Leonard says you're pregnant.
啥?
What?
"什么都不要说
"Don't say anything.
当她告诉你时假装吃惊就好"
Act surprised when she tells you."
好吧 你想怎么来?
All right, how you want to do this?
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
哦 天啊 简直不敢相信!
Oh, my God, I can't believe it!
太棒了!
This is so exciting!
嗯 我很激动
Yeah, I'm really exciting.
你难道不开心吗?
Are you not happy about this?
我当... 当然开心
I am. Of-of course I am. I'm...
肯定是荷尔蒙的锅
I'm sure it's just the hormones.
但太奇怪了 是Howie这几年来
But it's weird. Howie's the one who's been talking about
一直都在说生个孩子
having kids for years, and I was
我以为他会很高兴 就激动地告诉了他
all excited to tell him because I thought he'd be thrilled,
但他却抓狂了
but then he started to flip out
弄得我觉得这是个坏主意
and now this feels like a bad idea
而且我要长胖了
and I'm gonna get fat.
不会的 别这样 你不会长胖的
No, no, come on. Come on, you're not gonna get fat.
你会变得美丽又迷人
You're gonna be beautiful and glowing
并拥有世界上最可爱的大肚皮
and-and have the cutest little baby bump ever.
站着说话不腰疼 瘦婊砸
Easy for you to say, skinny bitch.
不好意思 是荷尔蒙
Sorry, hormones.
嗯 没事 我只听到了"瘦"
Oh, that's all right. All I heard was "skinny."
我认为Howard的反应跟你想的不一样
I wouldn't make too much out of Howard
也可以理解
not reacting the way you expected him to.
嗯 我敢肯定
Yeah, I'm sure
他只是被吓到了
it was just the initial shock of it all.
可能吧
You're probably right.
我们谈过之后他冷静下来了
After we talked about it, he started to calm down.
我根本不应该要孩子
I shouldn't be raising a kid.
我连我自己的蔬菜都不会吃
I don't even eat my own vegetables.
哥们 我认为你有些夸张了
Buddy, I think you might be overreacting.
还有这鼻子
And then there's this nose.
他要是长得像我怎么办?
I mean, what if he looks like me?
或者更糟...
Or worse...
要是个女孩像我怎么办?
what if she looks like me?
更别提
Not to mention
这对我们朋友圈的影响了
the impact on our social circle.
一切都会改变
Everything's going to change.
Howard不能像以前一样常来了
Howard won't be able to come over as much.
- 他可以带孩子过来啊  - 那我们还得
- Well, he could bring the baby here.  - Oh, but then we'd have to
给公寓装安全防护措施 跟你说 我姐姐
baby-proof the apartment. You know, my sister
就给她家浴室马桶上锁了
has one of those toilet locks in her bathroom.
我有两个博士学位 可还是被逼得尿在洗脸池
I have two doctorates, I still had to go in the sink.
天啊 你知道
Oh, my God, and do you have any idea
养个孩子有多贵吗?
how expensive having a kid is?
我看到说在洛杉矶 供个孩子到大学
I read that in Los Angeles, raising a child through college
花费超过一百万
can cost over a million dollars.
一百万?
A million dollars?
天 这感觉就像我的蛋蛋在蛋疼
God, it's like my nuts just kicked me in the nuts.
行了... 我现在就得开始
That's it... I got to start
多挣钱了
earning more money right now.
我有办法... 你可以让Bernadette
I know... you could ask Bernadette
多给你点零花钱
for a raise in your allowance.
这不是开玩笑
This isn't a joke.
我没有开玩笑
I wasn't joking.
不用担心
It'll be fine.
每天都有人生孩子
People have kids every day.
- 你会想到办法的  - 是啊
- You'll figure this out.  - Yeah, come on,
你也知道这是好事儿
this is great news and you know it.
嗯... 你说得对 是好消息
Oh... You're right, it is,
我只是... 有点不知所措
I'm just... a little overwhelmed right now.
嘿 你知道我们该干嘛吗?
Hey, you know what we should do?
一起结扎以防悲剧重演?
All get vasectomies so this doesn't happen to us?
出去庆祝
Go out and celebrate.
你还说过更难听的话
But not your worst idea.
嘿 我们做点什么让你分散注意力吧
Hey, let's go do something to get your mind off this.
- 嗯嗯 我们该出去  - 去哪?
- Yeah, yeah, we should go out.  - Where?
不知道 酒吧?
Uh, I don't know, a bar?
不能喝酒
Can't drink.
我们能 不过算了
We can, but all right.
你饿了吗? 你爱的那家寿司店怎么样?
Are you hungry? How about that sushi place you love?
医生说我不能吃寿司
Doctor said I can't have sushi.
好吧 我们不一定非要出去
Okay, look, we don't have to go anywhere.
我们可以留在这儿泡热水澡
We can just, you know, stay here and hang out in the hot tub.
医生说我不能泡热水澡
Doctor said I can't go in the hot tub.
或许你该换个新医生
Maybe you should get a new doctor.
怎么 他还禁止你笑吗?
What, he said you can't laugh either?
我建议为我们的朋友干一杯 Howard...
I'd like to propose a toast to our friend, Howard...
敬他宽阔的胸怀 美丽的灵魂...
his, um, his big heart, his beautiful soul...
还有那竟然没剥夺他
And his tight little pants
生育能力的紧身小裤子
that somehow did not make him sterile.
干杯
Cheers.
看这个
Well, look at this.
我敢说发明这小伞的人
I bet whoever invented tiny umbrellas
肯定不愁钱的事
doesn't have to worry about money.
他想生多少孩子生多少
He can have all the kids he wants.
还能给他们的脑袋遮一小片雨
And can keep a small portion of their heads dry.
我要是想好好养这个孩子
If I'm gonna have any chance of raising this kid,
我得想出个挣钱的大招
I need to come up with a big idea to make some money.
- 这应该不难  - 你说得容易
- There's no reason you can't.  - That's easy for you to say.
你和Sheldon早就提出了
You and Sheldon already came up with
超流氦模型
your superfluid helium model.
那只是研究 我们从中
That's just research. We're never gonna
挣不了钱
make any money from it.
管它氦不氦的 真正的超流体
Forget helium. The real superfluid
是这杯子里的水果酒
is the fruit punch in this mug.
让我想起了老爸秘制的
Reminds me of my daddy's secret
"别告诉妈妈"果汁
"Don't Tell Mama" juice.
这酒劲儿还是挺大的 你慢点喝
Uh, these are strong, you should slow down.
啊
Ah.
发明个这个怎么样...
Okay, how about this for an invention...
大... 一丁点的小伞
slightly... bigger cocktail umbrellas.
这怎么能算是发明?
How is that a new invention?
不知道 不过苹果公司不也就改改尺寸吗
I don't know, all Apple does is change the size of things
我们还是一直买
and we keep buying them.
是的说 我喜欢我的巨型iPad和小iPad
It's true. I like my giant iPad and my little iPad
快赶上对普通大小iPad的喜欢了
almost as much as my regular-sized iPad.
这个地方好棒
This place is terrific.
为什么我们从没来过?
Why... why have we never been here before?
很多乐子我们都不去找... 因为你
The same reason we don't do a lot of fun stuff... you.
一个脸都聚不上焦的人
That's some smart talk from a guy
还能说出这么机智的话
who can't even keep his face in focus.
厕所在哪里?
Where's the bathroom?
那边角落
Uh, it's in the corner.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
嘿 你们好吗?
Hey, how you doin'?
希望厕所标志明显
I hope the bathroom is clearly marked.
没关系
Doesn't matter.
反正他去了厨房
He's headed for the kitchen anyway.
这也许是个好主意...
Maybe that's an idea...
醉酒人士的导航系统
guidance systems for drunk people.
已经有了 叫优步
They have that. It's called Uber.
嘿
Hey.
在你们的过冷氦气实验中
In your supercooled helium experiments,
你们有制造出量子漩涡吗?
did you create quantum vortices?
有啊 怎么了?
Yeah. Why?
如果你制造一个指引系统
Well, if you made a guidance system,
可不可以用这些漩涡作为陀螺仪?
couldn't you use those vortices as a gyroscope?
哇哦 我倒从来没这样想过
Wow. I've never thought about that.
而且既然处于量子态
And since it's in a quantum state,
就可以保持永久的持续性
it would maintain an infinite persistence.
开创性的启示 鸡尾酒
Groundbreaking revelations, tropical drinks.
这简直是欲望都市中最精彩的一集
Tell me this isn't like the best episode of Sex and the City.
你可能确实想出了一个好主意
You may have actually just come up with something.
- 你真这么觉得?  - 当然
- You think so?  - I really do.
小伙伴们 这里的厕所简直棒极了
You guys, the bathroom here is amazing.
有人在里面做饭
There's people cooking in it.
想想当你有了孩子之后
Think about all the fun things you get to do
所有可以做的好玩的事
when you have a baby. Yeah!
你可以去买玩具和小衣服
Yeah, you get to buy toys and little clothes.
这些事我现在就在给Howie做了
I kind of already do that for Howie.
还有 不管你什么时候觉得饿了
And-and whenever you're hungry,
会发现地上到处都面包车和麦片
you'll be in a minivan with Cheerios all over the floor.
我给Sheldon找了一个新的旅行杯
Oh, and I just found a new travel cup for Sheldon.
每次只能三口三口喝
It only lets out three at a time.
你们是什么时候决定造人的?
So, when did you guys decide to get pregnant?
呃 我们并没有做任何决定
Well, we didn't exactly decide.
一直有说到这事
We were talking about it,
然后一个晚上我们就有点鲁莽
and then one night we got a little reckless.
- 说说看!  - 赶紧的!
- Oh, tell us!  - Yeah, tell us.
- 不要啦 我很不好意思的  - 快点说
- No, I'm embarrassed.  - Oh, come on,
大家都是成年人 都做过的
we're all grown-ups. We've all done it.
我! 我也是！我是一个成年人而且我做过了!
Me! Me-me, too! I'm a grown-up and I've done it!
好吧
Fine.
一天晚上我们外出
We were out one night,
然后事情就自然的发生了
and things got a little spontaneous.
感觉有八卦
Oh, that sounds juicy.
Sheldon一直在不同地说时区
Well, Sheldon was going on and on about time zones
铁路时间表什么的 我出去..
and railroad schedules, and I went out...
停 我想起来了 等下
Wait, I remember that. Hang on.
你们在我们那里做的?
You did it at our place?
貌似是在Sheldon床上
Kind of on Sheldon's bed.
什么?!
What?! No!
我当时要去厕所
I was headed to the bathroom,
刚好碰到Howie出来
and I passed Howie on his way out.
通常他会说 "不要进去那里"
Usually he says, "Do not go in there,"
但这次他说 "嘿 我们到这里面去"
but this time he said, "Hey, let's go in here."
- 你们怎么可以这样?  - 对不起
- How could you do that?  - I'm sorry,
但你知道的 和你男人在一起时会怎样
but you know what it's like when you're with your man
然后事情就这样发生了
and one thing leads to another.
我确实知道是怎么样的 真的
I do know what that's like. I really do.
我没看到有人
I'm not seeing anyone
这样利用液氦漩涡
using liquid helium vortices like this.
我也没找到
I'm not finding anything either.
这是个好迹象
That's a good sign.
等等 我发现一些
Oh, wait, I found something.
讨厌 发现什么了
Damn. What is it?
一段视频 熊猫宝宝打喷嚏
This video. The baby panda sneezes,
把熊猫妈妈吓坏了
and the mama panda gets so scared.
能不能集中注意到我们正在说的事情上来?
Can you focus on what we're talking about?
好吧
All right.
听着 这可能是酒后胡话
Look, now, this may be the rum talking,
只要漩涡的比率
but as long as the unpinning rate of the vortices
保持在1.1到1.3之间
is kept within 1.1 and 1.3,
马努格斯力的效应就是微不足道的
the Magnus force issue should be negligible.
就算喝醉了 他也比我们都要灵光些
Even drunk, he's still smarter than all of us.
而且强壮一些
And stronger.
谁想看我揍翻那个酒保?
Yeah. Who wants to see me beat up the bartender?
我很愿意看
I'd enjoy that.
算了 她是个好孩子
Nah, she's a good kid.
如果这个是可行的 我们就能申请专利
If this is a viable thing, we could get a patent
然后授权给制造导航系统的公司
and license it to companies that make guidance systems.
看啊 你才知晓自己成为父亲不过一天
Look at that. You've known you're gonna be a father
就已经开始进步了
for less than a day and you're already stepping up.
跟你讲 你肯定能搞定
I'm telling you, you got this.
也许你是对的
Maybe you're right.
他当然是对的
Of course he's right.
你和我都知道长大时没有父亲有多艰难
You and I both know how hard it is growing up without a father.
所以我确信你会
That's why I'm confident you're gonna be
成为最棒的父亲
the best dad you can be.
谢谢你 Sheldon
Thank you, Sheldon.
不用谢
You're welcome.
而且如果他生的是双胞胎 我们就能
And if he has twins, we can do
拿他们做各种有趣的实验
all kinds of neat experiments on them.
如果愿意的话你们可以进去
You guys can go in if you want.
算了 我们是一起的
No, we're a team.
如果你不能进去 我们也不进去
If you can't go in, we're not going in.
那为什么我们还要喝酒?
Then why are we drinking?
够了 她怀上的又不是圣婴 别那么认真
Okay, it's not like she's got the Christ child in there,
好吗?
all right?
是Leonard
Oh. It's Leonard.
他说Sheldon喝醉了 他们打算去K歌
He says Sheldon's drunk and they're gonna do karaoke
问我们要不要也一起去
if we want to join them.
好像蛮好玩
That sounds fun.
不好
Oh, no.
Sheldon喝醉了还给我发短信
Sheldon's drunk texting me.
说了什么?
What's it say?
你们要不要和我们一起去K歌
"Would you like to sing karaoke with us."
这哪里像醉了?
How is that a drunk text?
他结尾用的句号而不是问号
He used a period instead of a question mark.
简直醉成狗了
He's so wasted.
# 电影就要开始 你在路上等着巴士 #
# Your movie's showing, so you're going #
# 就算看过烂片五场 你也不觉慌张 #
# Could care less about the five you're blowing #
# 剧场开始变黑 剧幕就要拉开 #
# Theater gets dark just to start the show #
# 你瞅见有个美眉 #
# You spot a fine woman sitting #
# 坐在你同一边 穿着黄色裙边 #
# In your row, she's dressed in yellow #
# 她说 嘿 #
# She says, "Hello" #
# 旁边那个小哥 靠我再近一些 #
# "Come sit next to me, you fine fellow" #
# 没有半分犹豫 你流着哈喇子上前 #
# You run over there without a second to lose #
# 下面还有什么 嘿 #
# And what comes next, hey #
# 动一动 #
# Bust a move #
# 你渴求 #
# You want it #
# 你激动 噢 你渴求 #
# You got it, oh, you want it #
# 宝贝 你激动 #
# Baby, you got it #
# 动一动啊 #
# Just bust a move #
# 你渴求 #
# You want it #
# 你激动 噢 #
# You got it, oh #
# 你渴求 贝贝 你激动 #
# You want it, baby, you got it #
# 动一动啊 #
# Just bust a move #
# 你渴求 你激动 #
# You want it, you got it #
# 你渴求 #
# Oh, you want it #
大家伙 祝贺你们!
Hey, guys. Congratulations!
谢谢
Thank you.
你们玩的怎么样?
Hi. How are you doing?
太有意思了
Oh, wonderful.
我正随着音乐动一动
I'm being musically encouraged to bust a move.
如果我知道那是什么意思 我就照着做了
If I knew what that meant, I might just do it.
我很高兴你来了
I'm really glad you're here.
- 我们能聊聊吗?  - 当然
- Can we talk?  - Sure.
你过会儿也要上去表演吗?
So, you gonna get up there later?
一只麦 一个挂满
A microphone, a room
伪波利尼西亚宗教饰物的房间
full of inaccurate depictions of Polynesian religion,
还有一帮忠实听众 哥怎么能不上呢?
and a captive audience to hear about it? You bet I am.
我很抱歉自己今早这么失态
I'm sorry I freaked out this morning.
我希望你知道...
I want you to know...
我不会再害怕了
I'm done being scared.
觉得不安没什么的 我也很慌
It's okay to be nervous. I am, too.
谢天谢地 因为我说谎了 你想看别人尿裤子
Thank God, 'cause I was lying-- you might not have to wait
恐怕不用等到九个月以后了
nine months to see someone soil their pants.
但我也很兴奋
But I'm also really excited.
真心的
I mean it.
我也是
Me, too.
我爱你
I love you.
我不只是因为你胸部会变大
Mmm. And I'm not just saying that
才这么说的哦
because your breasts are gonna get bigger.
# 我们是一对吧? 女孩别再折磨我了 #
# Are we an item? Girl, quit playin' #
# 我们只是朋友 #
# We're just friends #
# 你在说什么? #
# What are you sayin'? #
# 看着我的眼睛告诉我你心里有了别人 #
# Say there's another and look right in my eyes #
# 我的初恋就这样第一次伤了我的心 #
# My first love broke my heart for the first time #
# 而我就像 #
# And I was like #
# 宝贝 宝贝 宝贝 噢 #
# Baby, baby, baby, ooh #
# 就像 宝贝 宝贝 宝贝 不 #
# Like, baby, baby, baby, no #
# 就像 宝贝 宝贝 宝贝 噢 #
# Like, baby, baby, baby, ooh #
# 我曾以为你永远属于我 #
# I thought you'd always be mine #
# 宝贝 我需要你的爱 #
# Baby, I need your lovin' #
# 必须完全享有你的爱 #
# Got to have all your lovin' #
# 宝贝 我需要你的爱 #
# Baby, I need your lovin' #
# 必须完全享有你的爱 #
# Got to have all your lovin' #
# 噢 宝贝 宝贝 #
# Ooh, baby, baby #
# 宝贝 宝贝 #
# Baby, baby #
# 噢 宝贝 宝贝 #
# Ooh, baby, baby #
# 宝贝 宝贝 #
# Baby, baby #
# 啊 加把劲吧 #
# Ah, push it #
我很感激 但你们真的不需要...
I appreciate this, but you really...
# 努努力再加把劲吧 #
# Push it real good #
# 就在我爸爸死去的地方 #
# Land where my fathers died #
# 是朝圣者骄傲的家乡 #
# Land of the pilgrims' pride #
# 从每一个山坡上 #
# From ev'ry mountainside #
# 就让自由 #
# Let freedom #
# 唱响... #
# Ring... #
我想把今晚的
I'd like to dedicate
最后一首歌送给我的妻子
my last song of the evening to my wife,
我的挚友 也是...
best friend, and...
我孩子的母亲
now the mother of our child.
我爱你 Bernie
I love you, Bernie.
# 孕育着我的孩子 #
# Havin' my baby #
# 是多么有爱的方式 #
# What a lovely way of sayin' #
# 说着你爱我 #
# How much you love me #
# 孕育着我的孩子 #
# Havin' my baby #
# 是多么有爱的方式 #
# What a lovely way #
# 说着你心里有我 #
# Of sayin' what you're thinkin' of me #
你逗我呢!
You're kidding!
什么奇葩会在别人的卧室里滚床单啊?
What kind of maniacs have coitus in someone else's bedroom?!
感谢你 帕萨迪纳! 晚安!
Thank you, Pasadena! Good night!
这个晚上太有意思了
That was such a fun night.
大概是因为你看见你家男人
Probably 'cause you got to see your man
在台上嗨翻全场吧
up there rockin' the mic.
是啊 你决定秀B-Box的时候
Yeah, yeah. I was a little surprised
我还真是有点小惊讶呢
when you decided to beat-box.
额 那其实是我哮喘发作了
Oh. That was really an asthma attack.
我就即兴发挥了
I just sold it.
我真为Howard和Bernadette感到高兴
Well, I am so happy for Howard and Bernadette.
我也是
Me, too.
这么说你也考虑过咯?
So, you ever think about it?
生孩子?
Babies? Mm-hmm.
这个嘛 现在还不急 不过总有一天是要生的
Well, I'm not in a rush but someday, yeah, sure.
你呢?
What about you?
我想我们会成为很棒的父母
I think we'd make amazing parents.
你俩能安静点不?
Will you guys keep it down?
不过说起来 我们还不够成熟啊
On the other hand, we might lack a certain maturity.